TYLER NELSON

(541) 480-7765 • tylerknelson@gmail.com • Bend, OR 97703

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking person offering outstanding telephone etiquette, social media and interpersonal skills. Well-trained individual with past experience working with children and elderly people. Punctual and dedicated to service and not scared to take on hard tasks.

SKILLS

- Public speaking
- Relationship building
- Novice SQL Experience
- Team collaboration
- Telephone etiquette
- Planning and Coordination

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sept 2014 - Nov 2014

Volunteer / The Ronald McDonald House

Maintenance of Property

- Was the leader of a project that went on for a couple of weeks.
- Had to demonstrate great teamworking skills.

June 2022 – August 2022

Landscaper / Naturally Designed Landscapes

Maintenance and Installation (Hard & Soft Scape)

- Was part of a small team and every role was important
- Very important talking with customers and what they wanted for each property

Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Landscaper / Oregon Vascular Specialists

Maintenance and Installation (Soft Scape)

- Needed to demonstrate leadership skills
- As well as planning where things needed to be planted and put and made a plan and executed it.

Jun 2017 - May 2018

Worker / Mountain Air Jump Park

Front Desk/ Floor Monitor

- Was able to work with computers and systems that the company had
- Needed to be able to talk with all different types of people in person and on the phone

EDUCATION

Past: High School Diploma

Current: Sophomore at Brigham Young University